http://www.hancockseed.com/pages/privacy-policy

Shop By Seed UseShop by Seed VarietyShop by ClimateSale ItemsHome
Bulk Seed Savings
Ordering more than 250 lbs. of seed? Bulk discounts automatically applied at checkout!
Total Weight
Savings
250-499 lbs.
$25 Off!
500-749 lbs.
$50 Off!
750-999 lbs.
$75 Off!
1,000-1,499 lbs.
$150 Off!
1,500-2,000 lbs.
$250 Off!
Over 2,000 lbs.
Sale Items
Aeschynomene (Vetch)
Aeschynomene (Vetch)
Aeschynomene (Vetch)
Aeschynomene Seed
Aeschynomene Seed (Vetch)
Contractor Seed Mixtures
Contractor Seed Mixtures (Cool Climate)
Contractor Seed Mixtures (Transition Climate)
Contractor Seed Mixtures (Warm Climate)
Deer Plots
Deer Vetch Seed “Aeschynomene”
Ryegrass Lawn Grass Seed
Ryegrass Pasture Seed (Annual)
Service Mixtures
Sesame Seed - (benne)
About Us
Why Farmer Direct?
Seashore Paspalum
Sesame - (Benne)
About Us
Why Farmer Direct?
Get a Quote
FAST, FREE SHIPPING
on hundreds of items!
Hancock Farm & Seed Company privacy policy
This privacy policy sets out how Hancock Farm & Seed Company uses and protects any information that you give Hancock Farm & Seed Company when you use this website.
Hancock Farm & Seed Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Hancock Farm & Seed Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 05/25/2018.
What we collect
Hancock Farm & Seed Company may collect the following information:
name and address
contact information including email address
information regarding previous purchases made at Hancock Farm & Seed Company
What we do with the information we gather
Hancock Farm & Seed Company requires this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Security
Hancock Farm & Seed Company is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
Hancock Farm & Seed Company uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Hancock Farm & Seed Company’s website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@hancockseed.com
Hancock Farm & Seed Company will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Need Help?
If you have any questions feel free to conctact us below.
1(800) 552-1027
Customer Service
Got questions? We don’t blame you! There are many things to consider when buying seed, and Hancock’s staff is happy to help you find the perfect solution for your needs!
Contact Us
1(800) 552-1027
Mon.-Fri. (8AM-5PM) Sat. (9AM-12PM) Sun. (Closed)
The Farm
18724 Hancock Farm Rd.
Dade City, FL 33523
Hancock Seed has been constantly introducing innovative ideas and custom seed solutions for our customers since 1978. Read more to find out how Farmer Direct brings you the best seed at the best prices.
Learn More
Seed Categories
Lawn, Turf & Service Mixtures
Food Plot & Hunting
Forage & Pasture
Wildflowers & Native Grasses
Homesteaders
Support
Newsletter Signup
Get monthly updates from Hancock Seed, including special pricing on Hancock Signature Seeds!
Submit
© 2020 Hancock Seed & Company
Privacy
Terms
Get Exclusive Offers
Sign up for Hancock Seed’s email service for exclusive offers and more!
Recipients can opt out of Hancock Seed’s email service at any time.
We Can Ship Worldwide!
Hancock Seed harvests, produces & exports the highest quality seed. No matter the project, our international sales team is happy to provide you with a quick quote for bulk seeds delivered anywhere in the world!
INTERNATIONAL QUOTE
Reset Password
Signature Series
Signature Series
Hancock's Grass Seed
Hancock’s Pasture Seed Mixtures
Hancock's Food Plot Seed Mixes
Other
Sesame Seed - (Benne)
Why Farmer Direct?
